C&sql Developer – Chance To Work In European Countries/ Salary Up To $1100
Codix
Immeuble Le Carat, 200 Rue du Vallon, Sophia-Antipolis, 06560 VALBONNE, FRANCE

Nộp Đơn
 Lưu việc làm này |  Gửi email việc làm tương tự |  Giới thiệu bạn bè
Mô Tả Công Việc
YOU WILL: 

Participate to the development of our software with C and SQL
Analyze client’s requirements
Design and develop new features according to detailed specifications

WE OFFER:

- Salary range: Attractive
- Competitive remuneration package including performance driven benefits: soft skill training, 13th month salary, project bonus, loyalty program, key person package, additional health insurance - Generali, lunch allowance, activities: company trip, football, volleyball ...
- Trainings and continuous investment into your professional development
- Friendly work environment with International working standards
- Unique career opportunities with a rapidly growing international company
*** Social and Health insurance: According to the current Government regulations
Yêu Cầu Công Việc
YOU HAVE:

-An university degree in computer science or equivalent technical area (last year students are accepted)
-Fluent usage of C, ANSI C, C++
-Good skills of SQL
-Conceptual knowledge of relational databases
-Good knowledge and experiences about Object Oriented Programming (OOP).
-Good command of English 

YOUR ADVANTAGES:

YOUR ADVANTAGES:
- Practical experience as a Developer
- Practical experience in UNIX-like OS (Linux, AIX, Solaris, HP-UX) 
- Knowledge of Oracle / Pro C / PL-SQL
- Good command of French is a plus


**Personality Requirements 
- Hard working, responsible, creative, strong interpersonal and communication skills. 
- Ability of working independent and teamwork

* If you are invited for an interview, you will be submitted to
- A technical skills test
- ORAL ENGLISH test.
Successful candidate might come in one of the European subsidiaries for 2 or 3 months internal training to our methods and product.

*** The interested candidates should submit full applications & curriculum vitae in WORD or PDF file and in English with full details of qualifications, experiences, current and expected salary, copies of certificates, one recent photo & contact phone number

*** Only applications and CV in English will be considered
-----
05 SQL Database Developers - Net Salary From 1200 - 500 USD
Aperia Solutions Vietnam Co Ltd.,
9th Floor, Hai Au Building. 39B Truong Son, Ward 4, Tan Binh District., HCMC

Nộp Đơn
 Lưu việc làm này |  Gửi email việc làm tương tự |  Giới thiệu bạn bè
Mô Tả Công Việc
General Information

Currently DB team has 25 members. We are seeking to immediately hire for 05 open job positions of SQL developer ranging from Junior to Senior level.

+ Candidates who is recently graduated need to have grades of Good or Excellence, ability to learn quickly, and problem solving skills. 

+ Candidates will have opportunities to be employed in appropriate positions depending on skills and experience

+ Senior position will have chances of being promoted to become Leader

+ Junior position will be trained and and mentored by company's Senior/Leader

Salary Range
+ Senior : From 900 - 1200 USD
+ Inter : From 700 - 900 USD
+ Junior : From 500 - 700 USD

Benefit: 

- Full benefit with social insurance
- Supplemental health insurance
- 13th month salary
- Opportunity for work and training in Aperia Solutions US

Job Description
+ Develop stored procedures, triggers, functions.

+ Design and create SQL DTS packages, ETL processes.

+ Provide code optimization, server performance tuning.

+ Support testing and database maintenance as required.
Yêu Cầu Công Việc
+ Have practical experience with SQL server.

+ Have experience or knowledge of working with complex databases that have huge amount of data.

+ Have knowledge of coding for, and processing of database of high level of structural complexity.

+ Possess skills of designing databases, index, partitions that strictly adhere to client’s specification.

+ Possess skills of tuning procedures and functions for high performance and optimal efficiency.

+ Be able to develop flexible procedures, functions, and databases which can be easily adaptable to frequently changing client’s requests.

+ Be able to communicate effectively on ideas, techniques, and problems with the whole team both in Vietnam and US.

+ Be enthusiastic about being a hands-on mission critical contributor and eager to improve and learn new skills.

+ Retain 3+ year experience of developing stored procedures, triggers, and transactions for SQL database server.

+ Candidate will have prospect and opportunity of being promoted to the position of Leader once desirable and higher skill demonstrated.
Chia sẻ  
Thương lượng
Cấp Bậc
Nhân viên
Ngành Nghề
IT - Phần mềm
Nơi Làm Viêc
Hồ Chí Minh
Ngôn Ngữ Trình Bày Hồ Sơ
Tiếng Anh
845 
Xem 27-05-2015 
Hết Hạn
Phúc lợi công ty
Cơ hội làm việc tại Mỹ
Lương tháng 13
Bảo hiểm sức khỏe
Thẻ Kỹ Năng Công Việc
English : Conversation, Reading, Writing Ssas, Ssrs, Ssis SQL Database 
Aperia Solutions Vietnam Co Ltd.,
9th Floor, Hai Au Building. 39B Truong Son, Ward 4, Tan Binh District., HCMC

Tên người liên hệ: Hai Le
Qui mô công ty: 25-99

Established since 2007, Aperia Solutions Vietnam( Former name : Data Delivery Services VN ) is a 100% foreign investment company. Our parent company is Aperia Solutions. Based in Dallas Texas with locations in Columbus and Vietnam, Aperia is the innovator in the financial industry, consistently bringing new technologies to better serve acquirers, ISOs, banks, and merchants. With decades of experience serving hundreds of financial institutions, we are the leader in payments technologies, consistently envisioning and delivering innovations to make business easier, more profitable, and more secure.

We were founded on the belief that we will provide precision tools – all with the speed and reliability required for our end users. That is our passion, skill and talent.

For more information about our products and technology please access our parent company's website at: http://aperiasolutions.com/

For more information about DDS company please access our website at: www.dds-data.vn

Currently we have 60 employees in Aperia Solutions US and 60 employees working for Aperia Solutions Vietnam. ( 25 members in Database team, 35 members in ASP.NET team, 30 members in BA/QCs ). We are expanding and hiring 30 more members of Web/DB/BA/QC team.